In ancient times there was a heavenly blade...
which gave its wielder great power: the legendary holy sword, Langrisser.
Greedy ambitions drove men to attempt to steal it...
While the righteous defended it with their lives.
Much blood was spilt.
However, the Baldea royal family, descended from ancient heroes...
has protected Langrisser throughout the ages.
But now, the peace is crumbling.
His majesty, Dalshis Emperor Digos, has gathered a massive army...
to lay siege to Baldea Castle and obtain Langrisser.
He wants to obtain the sword to realize his great ambitions of world conquest.
A long time has passed, and now the seal of the cursed sword has been broken.